buy1get1.in 2018-06-29

# Our Pricavy Policy - Buy1get1.in

## COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION:

Buy1Get1.in is commited to protecting your Privacy. For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes non-personally identifiable information only, e.g., the IP address, domain type, browser version, and service provider. Persons who supply us with their address, telephone number and/or email may be contacted by us with information regarding orders they have placed or regarding other operational information. We also store information volunteered by you that you may elect to provide to us when you register or update your account, enter a contest, participate in a survey, shop online, or make a purchase.  
We use the information we collect about you to improve the content of our website, product to improve order processing and order confirmations, respond to your inquiries and feedback, and to provide you with a better personalized shopping experience. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Buy1Get1.in. Buy1Get1.in reserves the right to share information collected hereunder with its own affiliates.  
In the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business assets, consumer information may be one of the business assets that are transferred as part of the transaction.

## YOUR OTHER PERSONAL INFORMATION:

Any payment information that is maintained by us is masked to keep it protected in the unlikely event of unauthorized breaches of security. In addition, we participate in cooperative database services. These services help us to direct print catalogs, mailings and other marketing initiatives to appropriate purchasers and website visitors. Names and mailing addresses may be shared between participating parties in the cooperative database services, but no credit card information or email addresses are provided to the cooperative.  
Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Buy1Get1.in reserves the right to disclose personal information as obligated by law, in response to duly authorized legal process, governmental requests and as necessary to protect the rights and interests of Buy1Get1.in.

##  **YOUR E-MAIL ADDRESS:**

We may store the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email and add you to our mailing list when you sign up to receive special promotions and updates. By electing to receive emails from us, we are able to send you exclusive information and special offers, which you may otherwise not learn about. Follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of these emails to cease receiving them. Requesting removal will not prevent you from receiving email communications relating to any online order you place with us. Buy1Get1.in does not currently sell, trade or rent your email addresses to others.

##  **USE OF COOKIES:**

We use cookies placed on your computers hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser during your visit to our site and when you return to our site. For instance, when you are ready to purchase an item, a cookie allows our site to "remember" you have added the item to your shopping cart. We can also show you merchandise based on your preferences and provide you with a more personalized shopping experience.

##  **CONDITIONS OF USE:**

Buy1Get1.in does not warrant that this site, its servers, or e-mails sent by us or on our behalf are Virus Free. Buy1Get1.in will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the use of this site. By visiting this site, you agree that the laws of the India without regard to its conflict of laws principles, govern this privacy policy and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and actoserba or its affiliates.
